

2+ years of experience as a Product Owner with an extensive background in software engineering. Nothing satisfies me more than creating a great product, solving problems, and contributing to the overall growth of the business. Looking for an opportunity in a fast-paced, growing company where I can leverage my experience to build outstanding products and then assist in customer success.

Work experience

Senior Product Owner

Hoang Phuc International, Aug 2022 - Present

Led to build Core Platform is the next generation of Order Management System to manage end-to-end the process of more than 15k sale orders per day at HPI. I took responsibility for proposing solutions that contributed to the growth of the business.

- Increased the speed of processing orders by 2.5 times.
- Successfully integrated with E-commerce Marketplace (Tiktok Shop, Shopee, and Lazada) to increase 15% the revenue of the online channel.
- Worked closely with the business team and stakeholders to propose product strategy, roadmap, and launching plan.

Product Owner

Be Group, Sep 2021 - Aug 2022

Took responsibility for building and developing the success of the driver experience and delivery services which handles more than 10M trips per month.

- Increased GMV of Delivery services by 30% by optimizing the utilization of drivers.
- Developed the driver incentive system, increased the driver's satisfaction and decreased manual work by 80%.
- Received 90% positive reviews from users in revamping UX/UI on the Driver App.
- Prioritized product requirements and ensured products aligned with company strategies and goals.

Product Owner

ZAMO Tech, Dec 2020 - Aug 2021

Took responsibility for building and launching E-Invoice service and Edtech product.

- Researched the market, interview potential customers, and analyze competitors to find opportunities, then build a MVP.
- Conducted customer research to understand the customer problems, then come up with solutions to satisfy their needs.
- Coordinated the entire development team up to 10 members (BA, Developers, Designers, QAs) using Agile/Scrum framework to ensure that the requirement is understood and release the product on time.
- Prepared manual guide and product materials for users and other related teams to align with product operation flow.

Contact me

≥ Idvhuy09@gmail.com

+84 987 137 889

n District 7, HCM City

Skills

Data Analysis

Agile Scrum

Critical Thinking

Problem Solving

Communication

Design Thinking

Customer Research

Time Management

Work experience (cont.)

Software Engineering

ZAMO Tech, Jul 2018 - Nov 2020

- Built RESTful APIs for multiple projects in multiple domains such as education, enterprise digital transformation, media & entertainment.
- Developed SaaS products with high availability, and high scalability based on the micro-services architecture.
- Worked on backend and frontend, familiar with tech stack below:
 - Backend: Java frameworks (Spring Boot, Quarkus), Quarkus, Elasticsearch, PostgreSQL,...
 - Frontend: Vuejs, Nuxt.js, Ant Design System, Material Ul,...

Education

Computer Science

Ho Chi Minh University of Science, Sep 2015 - Oct 2019

References

Thuan Tran - Sr. Product Manager

Ex One Mount, Ex Tiki, Ex VNG +84 963 247 901

Phuong Tang - Head of Engineering

Ex One Mount, Ex Tiki, Ex MWG +84 902 983 344